Daniel Carter Beard Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Oversize (Box OV 1-OV 2)
  Arranged and described according to the series and containers from which they were removed.
  - Family Papers (Box OV 1)
    - Beard, Harry
      - Printed drawing (Container 12A)
  - Miscellany (Box OV 2)
    - Nature scrapbook (Container 260)